<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="private_policy">Baibolat Privacy Policy
        respected user:
        Baibolat understands the importance of privacy to you and will do its utmost to protect your privacy. Please read, understand and agree to this Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as "Private" before submitting personal or private data to Baibolat. This policy").
        We have developed this policy to help you understand the content:
        1. How will Baibolat use your personal data?
        2. How will Baibolat use cookies and similar technologies?
        3. How will Baibolat disclose your personal data?
        4. Baibolat visits and modifies your personal data
        5. How will Baibolat protect your personal data?
        6. How will Baibolat deal with children’s personal data?
        7. Baibolat \'s third-party providers and their services
        8. How your personal data is transferred globally
        9. How to update this policy
        10. How to contact us
        Please note that this policy applies only to Baibolat consumer electronics products, including feature phones, smartphones, tablets, home devices, data cards, computer applications, tools, software, websites that display or refer to this policy.
        This policy explains how Baibolat handles your personal and private data and affirms Baibolat \'s commitment to privacy. This policy does not cover all possible data processing scenarios.
        1. How will Baibolat use your personal data?
        Personal data is information that identifies an individual when used alone or in combination with other information. This data is collected when you use a Baibolat product or service, including name, date of birth, address, ID number, phone number, account number, photo, and location and date of access to the product or service. Baibolat will only collect and use your personal data for the purposes described in this policy. The following examples illustrate the personal data we may collect and how we use it:
        1.1 Personal data collected by Baibolat
        We collect certain personal data, including name, profile photo, phone number, email address, age, and location. The following examples illustrate the types of personal data we collect.
        (a) Data you submit directly: Many of Baibolat\'s services allow you to create an account or profile. You may need to provide account information such as email address, shipping address, phone number, product information, time of purchase, and payment method. If you use the Baibolat service to share content with your friends, we may need to provide your friend\'s contact information, including name, profile photo, phone number, and email address. Some of Baibolat \'s services allow you to communicate and share information with others. All such communications are secure. If you encounter any errors while using a Baibolat device or application, you can choose to send the error details to Baibolat.
        (b) Service usage data: We collect system and application data from your device, including device name, system and application version, regional and language settings, device version, device identification code (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN) , geographic location (such as the location ID of the device location), service provider network ID (PLMN), usage habits, and IP address. We also record service access times, search query terms, and data held by cookies on the device.
        (c) Third Party Data: We will also obtain information about you from public and commercial sources, as permitted by law. We also get information about you from third-party social networking services, such as when you use Facebook or a Twitter account to log in to our site.
        1.2 How will Baibolat use your personal data?
        We will use your personal data for the following purposes:
        (a) fulfill the order; deliver, activate or verify the product or service; make changes at your request; and provide technical support.
        (b) Contact you with your explicit consent; send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you; invite you to participate in the Baibolat promotions and market research; or send you marketing messages. If you do not wish to receive such information, you can unsubscribe at any time.
        (c) Send you notifications of operating system or application updates and installations.
        (d) Provide you with a personalized user experience and personalized content, and activate after-sales service.
        (e) Conduct internal audits, data analysis and research to improve our products and services.
        (f) Analyze business operations efficiency and measure market share.
        (g) Improve customer communications and ensure safe and quality service to our customers.
        (h) Troubleshoot if you choose to send us the details of the error.
        (i) Synchronize, share, and store the data you upload or download and the data you need to perform uploads and downloads.
        (j) Improve our loss prevention and anti-fraud programs.
        1.3 Location-based service
        When accessing certain location-based services (such as performing searches, using navigation software, or viewing the weather at a location), Baibolat collects, uses, and processes the exact location or blurred location of your device. Pebble needs these locations to provide the above services. Baibolat collects your device\'s identification number (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN), device type, model, and real-time location data (accessed via GPS, WLAN, and service provider\'s network ID). The purpose of Baibolat\'s collection of location data is to provide and improve location-based products and services.
        We will ask you which applications you want to enable for location-based services. You can choose to turn off location-based services on your device and refuse to share your location data. For more information on how to disable location-based services, please contact your network operator.
        1.4 Collect and use non-identifying data
        Non-identifiable data is data that cannot be used to determine an individual\'s identity. For example, Baibolat collects aggregated statistics, such as website visits. The purpose of the data collected by Baibolat is to understand how users use their websites, products and services. In this way, Baibolat can improve its services and better meet customer needs. Baibolat may, at its sole discretion, collect, use, process, transfer or disclose non-identifiable data for other purposes.
        We will do our best to isolate your personal and non-identifiable data and use both. If personal data is doped with non-identifiable data, it will still be treated as personal data.
        2. How will Baibolat use cookies and similar technologies?
        2.1 Cookie
        To ensure that the site is functioning properly, we sometimes store small data files called cookies on a computer or mobile device. A cookie is a plain text file that a web server stores on a computer or mobile device. The content of a cookie can only be retrieved or read by the server that created it. Each cookie is unique to your web browser or mobile app. Cookies usually contain an identifier, a site name, and some numbers and characters. With cookies, websites can store data such as user preferences or items in the shopping basket.
        The purpose of enabling cookies for most large websites or Internet service providers is to improve the user experience. With cookies, websites can remember a single visit (using a session cookie) or multiple visits (using a persistent cookie). With cookies, websites can save settings such as the language of a computer or mobile device, font size, and other browsing preferences. This means that users do not have to reconfigure user preferences every time they visit. If a website does not use cookies, the website treats them as new visitors each time they open a web page. For example, if you log in to one website and go to another page, the website will not recognize you and you will be logged out again.
        Baibolat will not use cookies for any purpose other than those stated in this policy. You can manage or delete cookies based on your preferences. You can clear all cookies saved on your computer. Most web browsers have the ability to block cookies. But if you do this, you will need to change the user settings yourself each time you visit our website.
        2.2 Web beacons and pixel tags
        In addition to cookies, we also use other similar technologies such as web beacons and pixel tags on our website. For example, an email sent to you by Baibolat may contain a click URL that links to the content of the Baibolat website. If you click on the link, Baibolat will follow this click to help us understand your product and service preferences and improve customer service. A web beacon is usually a transparent image that is embedded in a website or email. With the pixel tags in the email, we can tell if the email is open. If you don\'t want your event to be tracked this way, you can unsubscribe from Baibolat\'s mailing list at any time.
        2.3 DoNotTrack(Do not track)
        Many web browsers have a Do Not Track feature that publishes Do Not Track requests to websites. Currently, major Internet standards organizations have not yet established policies to dictate how websites should respond to such requests. But if your browser has Do Not Track enabled, all of your Baibolat website will respect your choice.
        3. How will Baibolat disclose your personal data?
        Baibolat will not sell your personal data to third parties. However, Baibolat will disclose your personal data in the following situations:
        3.1 Disclosure with explicit consent: Baibolat will share your personal data with others after obtaining your explicit consent.
        3.2 Disclosure to Baibolat\'s affiliates; your personal data may be shared with Baibolat\'s affiliates. As a policy, we only disclose the necessary data.
        3.3 Disclosure to Authorized Partners (hereinafter referred to as “our partners”); certain services of Baibolat are provided by our partners. Baibolat may share some of your personal data with partners to provide better customer service and user experience. For example, when you buy a Pebble product online, Baibolat must share your personal data with a logistics service provider to arrange delivery or arrange a partner to provide the service. We will only process your personal data for specific, specific and legitimate purposes and will only disclose the data necessary to provide the service. Baibolat\'s subsidiaries or partners do not have the right to use the shared personal data for any other purpose.
        3.4 Disclosure based on law or reasonable ground: Baibolat may disclose your personal data if required by law, legal process, litigation or public and government authorities. In some jurisdictions, if Baibolat involves reorganization, merger or bankruptcy and liquidation proceedings, your personal data will be disclosed to the counterparty. Baibolat will also disclose your data in the presence of reasonable demand, for example, for the purposes of implementing the terms and conditions and for the purpose of protecting customers.
        4. How to access or modify your personal data
        You can manage your personal data, such as your account information, at any time, based on Baibolat\'s terms and conditions. You should ensure that all personal data submitted is accurate. Baibolat will endeavor to maintain the accuracy and completeness of personal data and update it in a timely manner.
        You have access to your personal data, with the exception of certain legal exceptions. If the privacy and information laws of some jurisdictions are different, we will comply with them. If you would like to exercise data access, please contact us. To be safe, you may need to provide a written request.
        You also have the right to delete or modify any personal information we hold about you. Baibolat will remove or modify such information at your request. To make such a request, please contact us. If we have a reasonable basis to believe that these requests are deceptive, unenforceable, or if local law does not provide access, we will refuse to process the request.
        5. How will Baibolat protect your personal data?
        Baibolat values the security of personal data. We use industry standard practices to protect your personal data from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage or loss. We will take all reasonable and practicable steps to protect your personal data. For example, we use encryption to ensure data confidentiality; we use trusted protection mechanisms to protect against malicious attacks; we deploy access control mechanisms to ensure that only authorized personnel have access to personal data; and we hold security And privacy protection training courses to enhance employees\' awareness of the importance of protecting personal data.
        We will take all reasonable and practicable steps to ensure that irrelevant personal data is not collected. We will only retain your personal data for the period of time required to achieve the purposes stated in this policy, unless an extension of the retention period is required or permitted by law. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but please be aware that no security measures can be done without impeccable.
        6. How will Baibolat deal with children’s personal data?
        Our products, websites and services are primarily for adults. Children may not create their own user accounts without the consent of their parents or guardians. For the collection of children\'s personal data with parental consent, we will only use or disclose this data if it is permitted by law, with the explicit consent of the parent or guardian, or the need to protect the child. Although local laws and customs define children differently, we treat anyone under the age of 13 as a child.
        If Baibolat finds that he has collected personal data about the child without prior verifiable parental consent, he will try to delete the data as soon as possible.
        7. Third party providers and their services
        To ensure a smooth browsing experience, you may receive content or web links from third parties (hereinafter referred to as "third parties") outside of Berbate and its partners. Baibolat has no control over such third parties. You can choose whether to access links, content, products, and services provided by third parties.
        Baibolat cannot control the privacy and data protection policies of third parties, and such third parties are not bound by this policy. Please refer to the privacy policies of these third parties before submitting personal information to third parties.
        8. How your personal data is transferred globally
        Baibolat offers products and services through resources and servers around the world. This means that your personal data may be transferred to or from other jurisdictions outside of the country where you are using the product or service. Such jurisdictions may have different data protection laws or even no relevant laws. In such cases, Baibolat will ensure that your data is equally protected by all applicable laws and regulations. For example, Baibolat will ask you for permission to transfer personal data across borders or to implement security measures such as data anonymity before cross-border data transfers.
        9. How to update this policy
        Baibolat reserves the right to update or revise this policy from time to time. Baibolat will send you notifications of changes through different channels. For privacy policy changes, we will post the latest version of our privacy policy on our website. We will also post a separate notice (such as an electronic notification) to remind you of any changes to the privacy policy.
        10. How to contact us
        If you have any questions, comments or suggestions, please send an email to Eaglephone.kz@gmail.com.</string>

    <string name="license_policy">End User License Agreement
        IMPORTANT: This Agreement is an End User Software License Agreement (hereinafter referred to as the "Agreement") between you (individual, company or any other entity) and the company that uses the Software (see Section 1.1 of this Agreement).  Please read this agreement carefully before using your Baibolat device or downloading the software update described in this agreement. Your use of a Baibolat device or download of the Software Update will be deemed to have been agreed to be bound by the terms described in this Agreement. If you do not agree to this Agreement, do not use any Baibolat equipment or download this software update. Subject to the Berblet Return Policy, you can return your Berblet equipment to a specialty store or authorized distributor that you purchased at the time to request a refund. The return policy is implemented in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations of the country of purchase. Software subject to this Agreement does not include open source software components as defined in Section 1.2.
        1. General provisions
        1.1 The software described in this Agreement means: (1) Software components provided with you in connection with the Berbrat Equipment, including but not limited to code stored on the Baibolat device and other embedded software, documentation, interfaces , content, fonts, and any data protected by the copyright of Baibolat or its licensors; (2) updates or upgrades to the software described in (1). These software do not include the open source software components defined in Section 1.2.
        1.2 The Baibolat equipment and/or its updates or upgrades may also contain software components (hereinafter referred to as "open source software components") that are protected by third-party copyrights and licensed by third parties. Such open source software components are distinguished by the license information provided in the device, which also indicates the open source software license for each component. Therefore, when you use these open source software components, the terms and conditions of the open source software license apply. This Agreement does not change any of your rights or obligations under this open source software license. In the event of any conflict between the license conditions described in this Agreement and the content of any open source software component in an open source software license, the open source software license shall prevail.
        1.3 Unless otherwise agreed, the software described in this Agreement shall be governed by this Agreement, whether stored in read-only memory, on any other medium or in other forms, or from an online download location authorized by Baibolat.
        2. End User Software License
        Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, you have the right to use the Software in a limited, non-exclusive manner on Baibolat equipment or computers (as defined in Section 1.1). Do not sell, transfer or use for any other commercial purpose.
        3. Use restriction
        3.1 Baibolat\'s technology or intellectual property may not be used to develop software, or to design, develop, manufacture, or sell third party equipment/accessories or licenses associated with Berburt equipment without prior permission from Baibolat.
        3.2 You can make a copy of the software and save it on your computer\'s hard drive or other storage media for archival purposes. However, the software may not be distributed or provided over the network so that it can be used by multiple devices or multiple computers at the same time.
        3.3 You may not sell, rent, lease, lend, sublicense or distribute all or part of the Software to third parties without prior written permission of Babel. However, you may transfer the entire license of the software to the other party once and for all while transferring the Baibolat equipment, provided that: (1) The transfer must include your Berbrat equipment and all Puebla (2) You may not retain all or part of the Software Backup; (3) The party receiving the Baibolat equipment and software has read and agreed to accept all terms and conditions of this Agreement.
        3.4 Except as expressly provided otherwise, you may not and agree that no other person may copy, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, or create derivative works of the Software.
        3.5 When using software for storage or reproduction, you need to obtain authorization from the relevant rights holders in a particular country or region. The material copying functionality provided by Baibolat Software is limited to the reproduction of material that is not copyrighted, the material you are entitled to, or the material that you have authorized or legally permitted to reproduce.
        3.6 You agree to abide by all applicable laws and regulations of the country in which the Software resides or is used when using the Software.
        4. Right retention
        Baibolat and its licensors enjoy and retain all rights and eligibility to the Software and retain any other rights not expressly granted to you by this Agreement.
        5. Privacy Policy
        Baibolat\'s Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") provides information about the data collected by Baibolat and the way Baibolat uses the data. When you use the Software on your device, Pebble will collect data from your device in accordance with this Agreement and the Privacy Policy.
        6. Agree to use the data
        6.1 You agree that Baibolat and its affiliates/licensors may collect and use the data from your device and that such collection and use is to facilitate the provision of services and products to you. In order to allow Baibolat to provide you with software updates or upgrades, product support and other product-related services, you also agree that Baibolat and its affiliates/licensors may collect system and application data from your devices. Includes your device name, system and application version, regional and language settings, device version information, device identification data (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN), location information (such as the ID of the region where your device is located), service offering Business Network ID (PLMN), MAC address, and IP address.
        6.2 If you choose to help Baibolat improve its products and services by participating in the Baibolat User Experience Improvement Program, Berblat and its affiliates/licensors can collect data from your device for analysis. The data collected includes your device configuration data, application statistics, and error log data. All data is anonymized before it is collected and processed.
        6.3 All data collected from your device can be processed or transferred to Baibolat and its affiliates/licensors in countries other than the country in which you reside. This means that the data can be transferred to or from jurisdictions other than the country in which you use the Baibolat product or service. These jurisdictions may use different data protection laws or may not exist. In this case, Baibolat will ensure that these data are provided with an approximate and adequate level of protection as required by all applicable laws and regulations.。
        6.4 Baibolat retains your data only for the time period required to meet the purposes set forth in this Agreement and the Privacy Policy, unless required by law or permitted for a longer retention period. Baibolat will take all appropriate technical and organizational steps to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of your data, but it remains to be noted that any security measures are not completely reliable.
        6.5 This consent statement may be revoked at any time and is effective immediately. In the case of withdrawal, the terms of termination of this Agreement as set forth in Section 8 shall apply.
        7. Update
        7.1 Although Baibolatt has no obligation to provide you with the Update service, it may still provide you with the software update.This Agreement governs the replacement or updating of supplemental software provided by breblatt, unless such update is accompanied by a separate End User License Agreement, in which case the latter will govern.If you decide not to download and use the updates provided by Baibolat, you understand that you may place the software at a serious security risk and may result in the software being unavailable or unstable.
        7.2 Some software features may be limited by version.Update to the latest version to enhance your user experience.Some software products have automatic updates, which can be automatically updated for you.The Automatic Update feature of pabharat software will only download updates via Wi-Fi, and you can disable this feature in the software\'s settings screen.
        8. Termination and continued validity
        8.1 This Agreement will take effect from the first day you install the software.You may terminate this Agreement at any time by permanently deleting, destroying and returning the software, all back-up copies, and all related materials provided by Baibolat at your own cost.If you fail to comply with any of the terms or conditions of this Agreement, Baibolat or its licensors have the right to terminate this Agreement at any time without notice.Upon termination, you must immediately cease using the software and delete all software and related materials that have been copied and/or installed on your device or computer.
        8.2 Article 6, 9, 10, 11, 12, 14 and 15 remain in force after the termination of this Agreement.
        9. Disclaimer
        9.1 You acknowledge that the Software is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, and to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, neither Baibolat, its licensors, affiliates or copyright holders. Any representations or warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to warranties of merchantability, quality of satisfaction, fitness for a particular purpose, accuracy, confidentiality, and non-infringement of third party rights. Neither Baibolat nor any other party warrants that the functionality contained in the software will meet your requirements, nor that the operation of the software will be uninterrupted or error-free.You are responsible for the choice of the software to achieve the desired results, as well as the installation, use of the software and obtain the results of all the responsibilities and risks.
        9.2 Installation of the software may affect the availability of third party software, applications or services.We do not warrant that the features or services included in the software will meet your requirements, or that the software and its services will be completely error-free/non-exploitable or will provide a continuous and lasting service.In addition, burble does not warrant that the software will be compatible with any third party software or services.
        9.3 You further acknowledge that the Baibolat Software and Services do not apply to failure or delay in the Berbapt software or services, errors or inaccuracies in the content, data or information provided may result in personal injury or serious physical or environmental hazards. The circumstances or circumstances of the damage, including but not limited to the operation of nuclear energy facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control systems, life support or weapon systems.
        10. Limitation of Liability
        10.1 Baibolat is not responsible for software use caused by misuse, misuse or unauthorized modification.
        10.2 To the extent that the applicable law does not expressly prohibit any profit, income, loss of sales, loss of data or purchase of substitute goods or services, property damage, personal injury, business interruption, business caused by the use or inability to use the software Loss of information, or any special, direct, indirect, incidental, economic, cover-up, punitive, special or subordinate damage, regardless of the theory of responsibility (contract, infringement, negligence or otherwise), cypress Lat and its employees, licensors or affiliates are not liable, even if they have been advised of the possibility of such damage. Some jurisdictions do not allow liability for personal injury, incidental or consequential damages, and this limitation may not apply to you.
        10.3 The total liability limit for all of Baibolat\'s damages (except for personal injury or death caused by Baibolat\'s negligence, subject to applicable law) does not exceed the price paid for your purchase of the Baibolat equipment.
        11. Technical Support
        Baibolat is not obligated to provide you with any technical support services for the software described in this Agreement.
        12. Export control
        You may not use or otherwise export or re-export the Berbrat Software unless authorized by applicable law and in the relevant jurisdiction in which the Baibolat Software is located.
        13. Communication
        All notices and communications should be in writing and sent by registered mail or by e-mail with a return receipt.
        14. Dispute resolution and law
        The verification, interpretation, modification, performance and disputes of this Agreement are governed by Kazakh law. In the event of any dispute concerning the content or performance of this Agreement, it shall be resolved through friendly negotiation. If it cannot be resolved through negotiation, either party can submit the dispute to the people\'s court with jurisdiction over the place where the agreement is signed.
        15. Complete agreement
        This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and Baibolat to govern the use of your software and will supersede any prior agreement between you and Baibolat regarding the use of the Software. When you use or purchase open source software, third party content, or other Baibolat services, you may also be subject to other applicable terms and conditions.
    </string>

    <string name="improve_policy">User Experience Improvement Program
        respected user,
        Thank you for choosing Baibolat and welcome to the EAGLE user interface. In order to enhance the user experience, you are invited to participate in the Baibolat User Experience Improvement Program (hereafter referred to as the "Program"). Please note that your participation in the program is entirely voluntary. If you choose to participate, please read this Privacy Statement carefully. By participating in the Program, you accept this Privacy Statement and agree to collect the following data from your device for analysis by Baibolat;
        (1) Your device identification data (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN), configuration data, system and application statistics, user behavior data, and error log data.
        (2) The plan needs to be connected to the network, and some data only supports uploading under the WL AN connection state.
        (3) Your data will be processed anonymously before being transmitted to Baibolat. Baibolat will analyze all the data collected to improve Baibolat\'s products and services and enhance the user experience.
        (4) To start or stop participating in the program, simply enable/disable data collection and transfer in Settings.
        (5) The data collected from your device will be securely stored in the cloud environment and will only be accessible when the data is processed for use in the program. Data transmission is subject to all applicable laws and regulations regarding privacy and data protection.
        (6) After the statistical analysis of Baibolat is completed, all data collected from your equipment for this program will be deleted.
        For all information collected from your device, Baibolat will remain strictly confidential. For more information on how Baibolat protects your data, identity and privacy,  please see the Baibolat Privacy Policy. </string>

</resources>